<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc><id>618</id><url>http://www.baidu.com</url><source>华师之声</source><title>News For Fun | 分手后的纪念品，你还留着吗？</title><datetime>2022-10-17 19:25:00</datetime><body>奇TheMuseumofBrokenRelationshipsinHollywoodmakescatharsisfromheartbreak.分手后的纪念品，你还留着吗？Agiantgreendinosaurpiñata.Apairofjeans.Adisplaycasefullofhalf-emptycolognebottles.Youmightlookatthese everyday items and think “yard sale，” and yet here they are inside the Museum of Broken Relationships， opening in the heart of Hollywood， California.It’s no accident that this museum is in L.A.， says Museum director Alexis Hyde. “Los Angeles is a place of crazy dreamers， who have come from far and wide to pursue things that have never happened before……Along with those big dreams， we get crushing defeats.”So it seems almost too appropriate that the museum is on Hollywood Boulevard; if there ever was an actual Boulevard of Broken Dreams， this would be a good candidate.Now， let’s look at some of the interesting items on display in the museum， and the deions by their donors， emotion-filled stories of relationships that are no more.One Thousand Origami Cranes (千纸鹤) But I appreciate the contribution he made to my life， even in leaving me… Mutually Loved Davida Font(Davida字体) As our relationship deepened， we collected about 200 sightings of Davida all over the world… Once we broke up， I still saw Davida everywhere.Vintage Cupcake Toppers(纸杯蛋糕小人) My husband and I were too "alternative" to have a wedding cake， so we had this dope-ass dessert spread and I sourced vintage cake toppers for months. Six years later， almost to the day， he dumped me over the phone.Spectrum of a star (一颗星的光谱) He said: look， at the time you were born， the light left this star... Every time I see the Orion constellation， I relive some sweet memories.Cheerleader Outfit (拉拉队队长裙) He was a Nebraska football fan so naturally I ordered myself a vintage cheerleader's outfit. The night he ended things I almost put the uniform on in anticipation of him getting home. Thankfully [I] opted for a flannel PJset instead.Vintage Stratton Compact(复古粉底盒)Vintage Stratton Compact(复古粉底盒) I didn't see him pocket it and was surprised when he handed it to me a few hours later， wrapped up in notebook paper...On its official website， the owner of the museum explains:The exhibits reflect the full range of human emotions. Some are sad; but many are amusing and hopeful and remind us that people change， grow and recover.这些展品展示了所有的人类感情。有些是悲伤的，但也有许多是有趣的、满怀希望的，提醒着我们人会变，会成长，会从阴影中走出来。Love relationships may end; relationships with family members， business partners， cities， religions and even with our former selves may end. But we learn and move on.爱情也许会结束，和家人、商业伙伴，和城市、宗教，甚至和过去自己的也会说再见，但是我们会从中学到些什么，并继续前进。The dislocation of a broken relationship may be isolating， but the experience is universal. No one is alone in this.失恋的痛苦或许只有自己知道，但这样的经历是人类共有的，没有人是孤独的。文案：张宇峥 | 编辑：和钰校对：周易图片整理自网络，版权归原作者所有VOC∣一个有用的公众号 长按，识别二维码，加关注 ■ ■ ■ ■ ■</body></doc>